Vishal Kandale

→ +91 9545328373 vishalkandale10@gmail.com linkedin.com/vishal

github.com/vishal

PROFILE

DevOps Engineer: 2.5+ years of IT experience in DevOps with Azure and AWS Cloud platforms. Good knowledge of Kubernetes and experience in Terraform. Associate Certified in Azure and AWS platforms. Experience in CI/CD deployment and management. Persistent's Annual Global Hackathon Semicolon 2024 Winner. Currently working as a Senior Software Engineer at Persistent Systems since Feb 2022.

Education

SPPU University May 2022

Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Engineering (CGPA: 8.70)

Nashik, Maharashtra

Experience

Persistent Systems Limited - Pune, India

Pune, Maharashtra

Persistent Systems Limited - Pune, India

Pune, Maharashtra

Persistent Systems Limited - Pune, India

Pune, Maharashtra

Senior Software Engineer - July 2024 to present Senior Software Engineer. Software Engineer

- July 2022 to present Software Engineer.

Software Engineer Intern

- February 2022 to July 2022 Intern.

Projects

Persistent Systems Limited - Pune, India

- Client: Deloitte | Role: DevOps Engineer
- Responsibilities:
 - * Managing Azure portal, Cost Analysis, Yaml Pipeline, Agent's installation on VMs.
 - * End to end experience on creating infrastructure on Azure using Terraform.
 - * Good Understanding of Cost Analysis.
 - * Automated ansible script for Agent installation on VMs.
 - * End to end experience on VMs related operation.
 - * Good Experience on CICD Deployment and management.
 - * Hands-on experience on raising Incident tickets, task using Azure boards.
- Environment: Azure Portal, Azure DevOps, Azure Repo, VS Code, Putty and WinSCP

Persistent Systems Limited - Pune, India

- Client: Persistent | Role: DevOps Engineer
- Responsibilities:
 - * Managing AWS, Azure cloud platform.
 - * End to end experience on creating infrastructure on AWS and Azure using Terraform.
 - * End to end experience on Jenkins CICD Pipeline.
 - * Deployed and maintained Flask applications in docker and kubernetes cluster.
 - * Experience in developing RESTful APIs using flask framework
 - Integrated Swagger UI for API documentation using Swagger JSON configuration in Flask.
 - * End to end experience on managing Git repository and Jira.
- Environment: AWS, Azure Jenkins, Docker, kubernetes, GIT, Jira and VS Code

Technical Skills, Certifications, and Awards

- 1. Technical Skills: Over 2.5+ years of experience with languages such as HCL (HashiCorp), YAML, and Python. Proficient in technologies including Kubernetes, Terraform, AWS Services, Azure, Azure DevOps, Docker, Jenkins and Git.
- 2. Certifications: 1] Certified Kubernetes Administrator (CKA), 2] HashiCorp Certified: Terraform Associate, 3] AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner certificate, 4] Microsoft Certified: Azure Fundamental
- 3. Awards: Persistent's Annual Global Hackathon Semicolon 2024 Winner, Recognized as the Best Performer for the GEMS FY'23 Batch, recipient of the Bravo-Individual Awards as the Topper for the GEMS Feb'22 Batch, and awarded the Bravo-Team Awards.